Oh ugly naked guy is decorating his tree. Oh my god you should see the size of his Christmas
balls. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey how much did you guys tip the super this year? Yeah we were
gonna give 50 but if you guys gave more we don't want to look bad. Oh actually this year
we just made them homemade cookies. And 25 it is. You gave them cookies? Money is so
impersonal. Cookie says someone really cares. Alright we're broke but cookies do say that.
I can see that. A plate of brownies once told me a limerick. Let me ask you something were
these funny brownies? Not especially but you know I think they had pot in them. So you guys who
else did you tip with cookies? The mailman, the super, oh and the newspaper delivery guy. Oh my
god. What? I don't think you're gonna like this. Oh gosh. Oh there's a cookie smashed in the sports
section. Oh look and he did my crossword puzzle. Yeah but not very well unless 14 Across Gershwin
musical actually is bite me bite me bite me bite me.
I can't believe it's Christmas already. You know I mean one day you're eating turkey the next thing
you know your Lords are a leaping and your geese are a laying. Which is why geese are so relaxed
this time of year. Hey guys. Hey. Hey Rich. I got you a little present. I'll open it. It's a slinky. Remember?
Huh? Walks downstairs alone or in pairs. Everyone knows it's just a big spring. All right you're still mad at me
because of the whole horrible and degrading list of reasons not to be with me. How about from now
on we just call it the unfortunate incident. Hey Gunther you got stairs in your place? Yeah. Yeah go
Hey guys. Hey. What's in the bag? Just some presents. Come on show us what you bought. You know you want to. Okay.
Okay this is a picture frame from Ben to my parents. I got some hers and hers towels for Susan and Carol.
And I got this blouse for mom. That is gorgeous. Look at these authentic fake medals. Tell you mom's
gonna be voted best dressed at the make-believe military academy. Hey. Hey. Happy Christmas Eve Eve.
Oh my god where did you get this? Macy's third floor home furnishings. This is my father.
This is a picture of my dad. Now Pheebs that's the guy that comes in the frame. No it isn't. This is my dad.
All right I'll show you. Baby I thought your dad was in prison. No no that's my stepdad. My real dad's
the one that ran in on us before I was born. How have you never been on Oprah? Okay look see this
is him. My mother gave me this picture before she died. Same guy. Honey uh this is a picture of the
frame guy posing in front of a bright blue screen with a collie. That's not a blue screen. It's just
I maybe it was just really clear that day. Okay I have to talk to my grandmother. Wait a minute honey.
So anyway I'm trying to get my boss's ex-wife to sleep with me. Oh but when Phoebe has a problem
everyone's all ears. Esther Livingston. Hi Pooh. Hi Graham. What you doing? Oh just updating the
phone book. Um Graham um can I see the pictures of my dad again? Oh oh sure sure uh how come? Just
you know to see him. Oh sure. This is the one of your father in a meadow and helping a little boy
fly a kite and here he is at a graduation. Another graduation. Another graduation. Okay is this really
my father? Well of course it is. I smell smoke. Maybe that's because someone's pants are on fire.
You know in all the years that we have been grandmother and granddaughter you have never lied
to me. All right that is not your father. That's just a picture of a guy in a frame. Oh god. It was your
mother's idea. You know she didn't want you to know your real father because it hurt her so much when
he left and I didn't want to go along with it but well then she died and and it was harder to argue
with her. Not impossible but harder. All right so well he's not a famous tree surgeon?
And then I guess okay he doesn't live in a hut in Burma where there's no phones?
Last I heard he was a pharmacist somewhere upstate.
Okay that makes no sense. Why would the villagers worship a pharmacist?
Honey. Oh yeah anyway that's all I know.
That and this.
This is the real him.
Oh.
You know I remember my father all dressed up in the red suit the big black boots and the patent
leather belt sneaking around downstairs. He didn't want anybody to see him but he'd be
drunk so he'd stumble crash into something and wake everybody up. Oh that doesn't sound
like a very merry Christmas. Who said anything about Christmas?
Hi. Hey anyone here from Phoebe yet? No nothing. I hope she's okay. Yeah I know
exactly what she's going through. How do you know exactly what she's going through? She told us.
So what you got there Monica? Just some stuff for the party. Hey what are you guys doing here?
Are you supposed to be Christmas shopping? You guys haven't gotten your presents yet?
Tomorrow's Christmas Eve. What are you going to do? Don't you have to be claymation to say
stuff like that? Oh by the way man I don't think the mailman liked your cookies.
Here are the ornaments your mom sent.
Well maybe the mailman liked the cookies.
We just didn't give him enough. Monica pigeons learn faster than you.
Hey Rach, you know what? I think I know what'll make you feel better. How about you
make a list about me? Forget it Ross. No I'm not gonna stand here and make a list. Okay you're whiny,
you are obsessive, you are insecure, you're gutless. You know you don't ever you don't
just sort of seize the day. You know you liked me for what a year and you didn't do anything
about it and uh oh you wear too much of that gel in your hair.
See there you uh all right you did what I said.
Yeah and you know what? You're right. I do feel better. Thank you Ross.
Yeah in Albany. Could I have the number of Frank Buffet?
Okay um in Ithaca.
All right um Saratoga.
Oneonta. All right you know what? You shouldn't call yourself information.
Hey. Hello grandma if that is in fact your real name.
Come on now Pooh don't still be mad at me.
How's it going? Oh not so good. Upstate's pretty big. He's pretty small. You do the math.
Well I think you're better off without him. Oh honey I know he's your daddy but well to me
he's still the irresponsible creep who knocked up your mom and stole her gremlin.
You know I just I just wanted to know who he was you know. Yeah I know. Okay
I wasn't completely honest with you when I told you that uh I didn't know exactly where he lived.
What do you mean? He lives at 74 Laurel Drive in Middletown.
If you hit the Dairy Queen you've gone too far. You take my cab. Wow thank you.
Now remember nobody else drives that cab. Uh-huh got it. Oh I'm gonna see my dad.
Thank you. Oh okay. Oh wish me luck grandpa.
Hey Phoebe here with the cab yet? Yeah she she brought the invisible cab. Hop in.
Well she better get here soon the outlet store's closed at seven. Hey don't worry I figure it'll
be two hours to Phoebe's dad's house. They'll meet, they'll chat, they'll swap life stories.
Even if Phoebe tells the one where she's an Egyptian slave girl we'll still have plenty of them.
Hey here you go. Hey hey.
Hey. Hey. Can you believe this? In like two hours I'm gonna have a dad.
Yeesh. Yeah big stuff. Okay let's go. Okay all right here you have to hold this. Okay.
Brake left gas right. Uh-huh yeah that's my cheat sheet.
Where's my seat belt? Oh no that side doesn't have one the paramedics had to cut through it.
Hey. Hey.
Come on just tell me please please. For the 16th time no I do not think you're obsessive.
Oh gosh it's hot in here. Rach get the heat. Ross can you turn the heat down please? Sure.
And by the way there's a difference between being obsessive. Ross the heat.
Fine okay you know heat heat heat and I'm the obsessive one.
Okay this way is on so this is off.
Did you just break the radiator? No no I was turning the knob and and here it is.
Well put it back.
It uh it won't go back. I'll call the super. Here let me try. Oh oh that's right I forgot
about your ability to fuse metal. Hey it's funny's cousin not funny. Hi Mr. Trigger.
Hi it's Rachel Green from upstairs. Yes somebody uh broke our knob on the radiator
and it's really hot in here. Yes it's it's hot enough to bake cookies.
Well do you think we could have a new one by six?
What no no Tuesday we can't wait until Tuesday we're having a party tonight. Okay
tip the man. No if he doesn't like our cookies too bad I'm not gonna be blackmailed.
Look if worse comes to worst it gets a little warm we'll call it a theme party. Hey here's
a theme come on in live like bacon. Oh this is it 74.
Oh so that's what this is for. Wow this is it I'm gonna meet my dad.
This is like the biggest thing ever huh? Yeah sure is. Okay here I go I'm going in. All right
good luck Pheebs. Okay here I go.
Here I go. I'm going.
Hi welcome to our tropical Christmas party. You put your coats and sweaters and pants and shirts
in the bedroom. It's hard to tell because I'm sweating but I use exactly what the gel bottle
says. An amount about the size of a pea. How how can that be too much?
Ice ice ice squares anyone? Take a napkin all right. Monica Monica Monica your guests are
turning into jerky okay. Really I'm definitely comfortable. Hey hey hey get in line buddy I was
next. Mr. Traeger. You said there was a party. Oh yeah well hey welcome to our sauna. Is it hot?
My body always stays cool probably because I have so much skin. Hey geez.
All right all right here's the chance Monica give him cash. Rachel give him your earrings
something now anything. No I will not cave. Yeah I'm with Mon. All right all right you know how you
say I never seize the day. Well all right even though he's your super I'm seizing.
Mr. Traeger here is 50 bucks. Merry Christmas. Oh wow I didn't get you anything. Here's five back.
No no no that's that's your Christmas tip all right. Oh hey do you think there's a chance
you can fix that radiator now? No can do like I told the girl I can't get a new knob until Tuesday.
Ross. Yeah. Looks like he's playing baseball. You mean hardball?
Whatever. What you gonna do? Excuse me I'm seizing. Mr. Traeger here's another 50.
Happy Hanukkah. Will uh will this help with the knob getting? No the place is not open till Tuesday.
Am I not saying it right?
So wait you really did like my cookies? Oh yeah they were so personal really showed you cared.
Nice seizing gel boy.
So uh is this uh mistletoe?
No no uh that that is basil.
Ah because it was mistletoe I was gonna kiss you. Yeah no it's still basil.
Okay. How far did you get? Mailbox. All right we're getting closer.
Pheebs what's going on? No it's just like you know it's a whole mess of stuff you know
because like yesterday you know my dad was this like famous Burma tree surgeon guy and you know
now he's a a pharmacist guy and. Well maybe he's maybe he's this really cool pharmacist guy. Yeah
maybe yeah you know and and I'll knock on the door and and he'll hug me and I'll have a dad
you know and I'll I'll go to his pharmacy and everyone will be really nice to me because you
know I'm Frank's daughter you know. Well so why not go knock?
Well because I mean what if what if he's not this great dad guy?
I mean what if what if he's just still the dirtbag who ran out on my mom and us?
You know what I've already lost a fake dad this week and
I don't think I'm ready to lose a real one.
Pheebs that's okay you took a big step today. Yeah? Yeah and someday when you're ready
you'll make it past the hedges. Yeah. And when you do he'll be lucky to have you.
You guys.
I'm sorry about your shopping. Oh that's okay I'll figure something out.
Listen Pheebs I know you're not going in there but do you think it'd be all right
if I went and used his bathroom? That's fine never mind.
Cool snow kind of like a blank canvas.
Pheebs.
Oh holy crap is it hot in here.
Really? Hey you mind if I turn the heat down? Hey we could have used that kind of thinking earlier.
Hey Pheebs how'd it go? Oh I couldn't go in. Oh honey I'm sorry. Are you okay? Yeah yeah no it's
okay because I mean I know he's there so that's enough for now. Hey guys it's after midnight.
Merry Christmas everyone. Merry Christmas.
Hey Monica the knob was broken so I just turned it off from underneath I hope that's all right.
Aw thanks. Okay I guess that just leaves the gifts from Joey and Chandler.
Rach these are for you. Wiper blades. I don't even have a car. No but with this new car
smell you'll think you do. Okay Pheebs your turn.
Oh toilet seat covers.
Is that what you were doing while I was getting gas? You guys. Okay and for Ross Mr. Sweet Tooth.
You got me a cola drink? And a lemon lime.
Well this this is too much. I feel like I should get you another sweater.
And last but not least
the rib for your pleasure.
Thank you.